I consider it incredibly important that when you see something misrepresented, you correct it.
For instance, like when you see woke misrepresented, correct it.
When you see CRT called Black History, correct it.
When you see DEI called a lowered standard, correct it.
And in this case, when you see these news sources, mainstream media, calling being pro-Palestine as being anti-Jewish, you have to correct it.
FBI associated with New York City's Columbia University told Jewish students to go home this week following pro-Palestinian demonstrations on campus.
Writing today in an email, Columbia University's public safety and the NYPD cannot guarantee Jewish students safety.
When students are subject to hostile environments because of their faith or ethnicity, schools must act.
Students must be safe to learn.
It is absolutely heinous that they are misrepresenting these students and what they are standing for in this way.
It is not only deleterious to the actual value and merit of their news platforms and of Columbia, but also it is not safe for Jewish people to continue to fearmonger them.
That actually is harmful to their own psyche.
This is not any way dangerous to Jewish people.
They are asking for a divestment from Israel, which is an apartheid state.
These students are righteous in their indignance and we stand for them and we stand beside them.
Free Palestine.
Also, Karine Jean-Pierre.
So does that include Palestinian students?
Uh-uh.